Are those my things?
What are you going to do?
I'm replacing all your old clothes
with new ones.
Outfits that suit you better.
And as for this,
let's change this to a newer model
with a more secure connection.
Baste, you take care of that.
How is she?
We haven't talked to each other.
Why, did you fight?
No, we didn't.
I tried to call her
but she cannot be reached.
I don't think it's a matter
of WiFi or signal.
Knowing Rogelio,
they took away Florence's cell phone.
Why would they do that, Grandpa?
You must understand, Nero,
that the Almeros are a very proud family.
They are one of the oldest families.
And they are very sensitive
with their reputation.
And now that Florence is with them,
I'm sure she's going to be changed
and become an Almero.
Florence, can we talk?
Can we talk later?
I'll find a way to talk to you.
We're your friends, Florence.
We're not a threat.
- Are you okay?
- Hey Mister, don't push!
- Hey, that's enough!
- Don't push us!
Mister, they're not my enemies!
- Don't do that.
- Hey, stop!
- I said don't push us.
- Mister, stop it.
They are not enemies! They are my friends!
My child, this is Mother.
And Father, too.
Mother, Father...
Florence, we miss you so much.
Your father and I are always praying for you.
We also hear Mass and say a novena.
I heard your conversation earlier.
It's good that you're able
to eat properly there.
Do you want us to send you rambutan?
No need, Father.
I might burn down the whole mansion.
Don't be shocked that
we're here in the mansion.
Yes, Florence,
Grandpa Garp hired us to cook for them.
That's good.
Tristan asked me to make a mango pie
with Guimaras Mangoes.
And Troy wanted a Paella Valencia,
a Ventura, and Negra too.
So I hit him with the Paella pan.
And I suddenly made sushi.
Aldus was dreaming about sushi,
and I felt like I was having a nightmare.
Owen is my favorite because he likes eggs.
I told him to eat hot dogs too.
Oh, Mother, Father,
they're just pranking you.
Just have a little more patience.
Don't worry about us, Florence.
We can handle these brothers.
And Florence,
the Ferell Brothers is a misnomer,
because the truth is, they're all cousins.
It should be Ferell Cousins.
Yes, that's right.
Those brothers are a misnomer.
Do you already know their WiFi password?
Thank you, Nero.
Thank you for doing this.
Did you come up with this idea?
I don't want to take all the credit,
but yes.
Everything was my idea.
So yes, I'm taking all the credit.
I thought you'll try to be humble,
but you're still arrogant.
I miss you.
I miss you so much.
Really?
Maybe you're just saying that.
It's true.
If it's true...
What in particular do you miss about me?
A lot.
What in particular?
Too many to mention.
You're annoying.
If you don't answer me, I'll beat you.
Well, that's one of them.
I miss your snarl...
Your snarl of love.
I don't know about you.
That's another one.
You being dismissive when you're thrilled.
Am I very predictable?
Never.
Every day you surprise me,
just like right now.
You surprised me
that you were able
to handle this big change in your life.
I am admiring you more and more.
And I love you so much more.
Celestina?
Yes?
Are you okay?
Thank you, Grandpa Garp,
for helping me and Lydia.
We will consider this
a huge debt of gratitude.
I told you that Florence is
already a member of this family.
And even if she changes her surname,
she will remain a member of this household.
Excuse me, Don Ferell.
Has someone seen the real killer
of Florence's real mother?
As a matter of fact, no one has yet.
According to my research,
the death of Alyanna Almero remains unsolved.
Unsolved or unresolved?
Dissolved.
That's what I'm afraid of.
There's still a threat to Florence's life,
because there's still a danger
with the Almeros.
Wait, do you remember anything that night
when you found Florence?
Do I still remember anything?
Careful.
What's with you?
Maybe you need a wheelchair.
Do you need a wheelchair?
My tummy hurts. I feel so heavy.
Why wouldn't your tummy hurt
when you sucked all the brain?
What's with you?
You know me, I'm fond of brainy.
- Brainy?
- Especially when it comes to the beef broth.
Don't complain because
you ate a lot too, okay?
Well, I didn't eat.
What do you mean you didn't eat?
I ordered three cups of rice,
but you took another one.
Wait, I feel dizzy.
Oh no, that's what I'm telling you.
Okay later, let's drink medicine.
What medicine?
Well, I'll take care of it.
Let's go, you're sleepy, and your head hurts.
Let's go home.
- Let's go.
- I feel dizzy.
Okay.
Mister, have you seen a woman pass by here?
No.
No?
Okay, thank you.
What was that? He suddenly...
Addicts nowadays...
Do you remember what this guy looked like?
Did you recognize his face?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm having allergies.
Maybe I'm not used to staying in
a very clean room.
Look, I don't blame you
if you don't want to see or talk to me.
I just came here to say... I'm sorry.
I know I might have been
too harsh with you earlier,
but I hope you can understand
where I'm coming from.
I lost you once, Celestina,
and it broke my heart.
Now that I have you,
I will do everything to protect you.
But the Ferell brothers
have become my friends.
And I've become close to Grandpa Garp
because I spent a long time with him.
We're like one family.
Do I really need to avoid them?
I'll show you something.
I can't remember.
Just relax.
Don't be pressured.
You'll eventually remember.
Federico, maybe we should
shake your brain a bit
so you can remember the details.
You know, buddy, that's effective.
Even if you hit your head with a stone.
Stop it, both of you.
You're full of nonsense.
What if I hit your brains?
Babycakes, just relax.
We need to lighten the mood.
I don't want Federico to get stressed,
because he has a heart ailment.
Don't get pressured, Federico.
Take as much time as you want.
But no matter how small the detail
you remember...
Give it to us.
Maybe that can help us protect Florence.
She was the love of my life.
You should've known her.
It's unfortunate
that we spent so much time with her,
while you weren't able to know her.
Actually, I always dream about her.
Ouch.
Really?
Yes, I always see her face in my dreams
but I don't know if it was just a dream
or a memory that she left in me.
Maybe it's both.
She left the memories to show you
how much she protected you
with all her heart.
And the dreams are her way of saying
to be careful with our family's enemies.
She was killed by the Ferells, Celestina.
They killed your mother.
That's why I believe it's time to cut
all your relations with all the Ferells.
I know it's difficult to believe...
but they are the only ones
who have a reason to do this.
What's happening?
I don't know with this guy.
What are you doing?
The target was either me
or your grandfather that night.
It just so happened
that it was you and your mom who were in the car,
and not me.
Your mother protected you.
And I believe she sacrificed her life
saving you.
That's why...
I vow to do everything just to protect you.
That's why I hope you'll understand
this favor I'm asking you, Celestina.
Cut all your ties with the Ferells.
They are a threat to our family.
And most importantly...
you must never forgive them
for what they did to Alyanna.
She was killed by the Ferells, Celestina.
They killed your mother.
That's why I believe it's time to cut
all your relations with all the Ferells.
Your mother protected you.
And I believe she sacrificed her life
saving you.
That's why...
I vow to do everything just to protect you.
That's why I hope you'll understand
this favor I'm asking you, Celestina.
Cut all your ties with the Ferells.
They are a threat to our family.
And most importantly...
you must never forgive them
for what they did to Alyanna.
Hello, Florence?
Why?
Do you miss me already?
Nero...
we need to talk.
Oh, you're there.
I'm always here, but you barely notice me.
Wow.
Here, ham?
Hey, buddy.
How was your sleep? Was it good?
The truth is, I didn't sleep well last night.
We're the same, Federico.
I barely slept.
I stayed up late watching
"Strangers in the Nights of Things".
The twists are beautiful.
You thought all the characters
are nothing but...
Iking, don't be a spoiler.
And you even have an account,
but you refuse to share it.
No, I just used the password
of my ex-girlfriend.
She still hasn't changed it.
May I borrow the password?
Okay.
Actually, the reason why
I wasn't able to sleep well last night
is that I kept thinking
about what Don Ferell said.
We should know who killed Alyanna.
So we can be sure that Florence is safe.
Anyway...
don't you remember anything, buddy? Anything.
Well, I didn't eat.
What do you mean you didn't eat?
I ordered three cups of rice,
but you took another one.
If you think about it.
Wait, I feel dizzy.
Oh no, that's what I'm telling you.
Okay later, let's drink medicine.
What medicine?
Well, I'll take care of it.
Let's go. You're sleepy, and your head hurts.
Let's go home.
- Come on.
- I feel dizzy.
Okay, let's go.
Mister, have you seen a woman pass by here?
No.
No?
Okay, thank you.
Just a little.
Maybe I can remember
the shape of the head, the shape of his eyes.
You know...
why don't we ask someone to draw a sketch?
If there's a suspect,
they make a drawing, right?
Yes, that's right. There's a name for that.
Cartographic sketch artist.
Yes, that's the one.
That's me.
You haven't asked...
Good thing you asked.
Before I became a mailman,
I was a former cartographic sketch artist.
That's the position I applied for
in the municipal's office.
But the thing is, they made me a mailman.
Wow.
From cartographic, to gardener, to mailman?
I need to earn money.
I need to find a side hustle.
Before, there was a movie,
and they made me an extra.
And do you know what the role is?
Boy-next-door.
Dramatic actor.
I can do everything.
I need to save,
so you know, I can settle down with my girl.
Really?
Do you have a girl?
Well, do you think you're the only one
who has Babycakes in this story?
Wait, wait. We might go off-topic.
Is it true that you can draw?
Yes. That's true.
Just tell me, and I'll take care of it.
Let me know what he looks like.
I'm sorry, Ms. Florence Almero,
but they cannot go inside the school.
After the incident that happened last time,
I cannot risk another commotion happening
inside the school premises.
I'm sorry, Ms. Almero,
but I have made my final decision.
I cannot and I will not allow
your security people
to get inside the premises of this building.
Just wait for me outside.
But Ms. Florence,
your grandfather instructed us...
To keep me safe.
- Yes.
- That's right.
Yes.
Don't worry,
I think nothing bad will happen to me
inside the school.
And Dean is right.
We attracted conflict on the first day
that compromised the security,
and that's you.
But if I need you,
I will call you as soon as possible.
Okay.
Let's go.
Thank you, Ms. Florence.
You handled that really well.
You are truly one of our brightest students.
You're welcome, Dean.
By the way, come with me.
There's something we need to talk about.
Dean Alvaro, my grades are okay.
They're all good, right?
Why do you need to talk to me?
Am I in trouble?
Will I be suspended
because of what my bodyguards did?
The truth is, I don't want that,
but there's nothing I can do,
because that's what my daddy wants.
Just follow me.
But why do you have to talk to me
when I didn't do anything?
It's because there's someone
who wants to talk to you, Florence.
I spoke to Nero last night,
and he was telling me about your concerns.
Is it true that you have something to do
with what happened to my mommy?
Lorenzo was right.
Our business rivalry became intense.
I was so mad, I was able to say bad words
to Rogelio, in front of Lorenzo.
I was fuming mad, but I was in pain.
I was angry at the prospect
of losing my wife.
I vented out my anger
towards the business ventures with Rogelio,
that's why I said bad and hurtful words
in front of Lorenzo.
But your Grandma Amanda made me realize
not to get mad
and accept the time that we have.
She lived for years.
But she saw and got to know
her five grandchildren.
It was a struggle...
and every moment of it was special.
I have many sins, Florence,
but I can never do
what Lorenzo is accusing me of.
I can't deprive you of your right
to know your own mother...
and have a complete family.
Florence, sorry, but there's trouble again.
What do you mean there's trouble?
It's your bodyguards and the Ferells.
They're fighting again.
- Where?
- Over there.
These heels are such a problem.
Hey Ferell guys, what did you do again?
This spells trouble again.
What's so funny?
What?
- Surprise!
Group hug!
Turn around.
- Let's go!
- Yes.
Okay guys, let's set some ground rules.
No more talking about Florence
being an Almero.
Okay, that's enough.
In this space, she is just Florence.
Besides, there are a lot of things
we need to talk about,
like, how is she and Nero.
And what's the stage of their relationship.
There you go.
And you're asking me those questions, Lina?
Shouldn't we be talking
about you and Troy now?
What? Hot seat.
What?
We just followed your advice, Florence.
We're not yet there, but it's getting there.
Wow...
So now it's my fault?
I already helped.
Wow, that's so thrilling.
Well as for me and Tristan,
we're getting there too.
Hey, stop it.
The last thing I want in this world
is to be your trophy boyfriend.
Hey, you're too harsh.
But that's impressive,
because Tristan prefers a more profound
and meaningful relationship.
- That's my bet.
- Trophy husband?
It's possible!
It's really possible.
Oh, by the way guys...
Let's make Aldus and Aira our role models.
They're just chill.
What do you mean just chill?
Aldus decided that we should stay friends.
Aira, you're nice, I already told you that.
But believe it or not,
I'm not thinking about relationships
like that yet.
That's because you're just a playboy.
Sounds like an excuse just to say no to Aira.
Of course not, Antonia.
Aira is an amazing person,
but I hope one day our paths will cross,
and when we see each other again,
we both want the same things in life.
Wow.
Well, you're just a playboy.
If our paths really do cross, Aldus,
probably I'm taken already.
By Aldus Ferell?
Possibly, dating Tom Holland.
- You're something else.
- What a pity for Zendaya.
- Yes.
- Don't you like Gagamboy?
How about you, Owen?
Well actually, I'm with Aldus on this one.
Dating isn't really my priority right now.
- I want to travel.
- With Antonia.
- Explore the world.
- By myself.
- With Antonia.
She's your world.
Hey, that's cool.
No, but that really just sounds
like a fun idea.
How about you, Florence? Do you have plans?
Do you have any plans?
Come on, take that bite.
- Yes!
Oh, let's take a selfie for this cute moment.
Right, guys?
- Let's remember this.
- Troy?
Take a photo for us.
- Let's do a selfie.
- Selfie!
So, you want a selfie,
but you want me to take a picture?
Yes.
- One, two, three.
- Take one without you.
One, two, three.
- Wacky!
Well, it's like...
Maybe the same as my head,
but a little more...
Maybe the cheeks are chubby.
Wait, chubby cheeks?
James?
And you have all the food.
How can we eat breakfast?
- Go ahead and get some.
- Huh?
You're something else.
That's why you're not being noticed.
And, then?
And I'm sure his eyes are scary.
It's like he won't do anything nice.
What?
Did you get it?
You know what, Federico?
I think I know the person you're describing.
It looks like he won't do anything good.
Is this the one?
You know, you're full of nonsense.
But in fairness,
the way he looks, he won't do anything good.
Well, I tried to draw it
based on what you're saying,
but it's really vague.
It's worse than my love life.
And you even blame others.
You know, Federico, let's just be patient.
You'll eventually remember his face,
and how he looks like.
My grandfather once said...
Why is your grandfather included here?
that if you return
to the scene of the crime...
it might trigger
and make you remember what happened.
In fairness to your grandfather,
he has a point.
Federico...
Why don't go back to the scene of the crime?
You're right.
That's a good suggestion.
Let's do that.
Yes.
Why didn't you answer Antonia?
That's because...
I don't know what to answer.
It seems for the first time in my life,
I have no plans.
Imagine, my dream before...
was just to finish my studies on time.
And support my parents...
and bring them to Europe and Boracay.
These are the dreams of a simple person.
Well, with my situation right now,
it's difficult to dream.
How can you dream
if you have an influential family?
How does an Almero dream?
The truth is...
even I have no idea what to do tomorrow.
But I only know one thing for sure.
Whatever is waiting for me in the future...
I want to be with you.
Wow.
My heart has really fallen for you.
I don't know
what kind of future is waiting for us.
But what I only know is...
I love you so much.
And I love you so much too,
Nero Sebastian Araneta Ferell.
What's this about, Garpidio?
You know what this is all about.
This is about Florence.
She is my granddaughter...
and you don't have anything
to do with her life.
That's where you're wrong, Rogelio.
Florence has been with us,
and she's been a part of our family.
Come on, Garpidio.
Do you really want
to get everything that I have?
I didn't get anything from you, Rogelio.
Enough already.
I look up to you like a big brother.
I treated you like a real brother.
And what did you do to me?
You took Amanda away from me...
even if you knew that I love her so much.
And now here you are,
trying to take her, Florence,
away from me and my son.
I'm sorry
if you thought I took Amanda away from you.
Sorry... That's what you're good at.
Saying sorry.
Maybe you should also be sorry
for Alyanna's death.
Do you really believe
I am capable of killing Alyanna?
I was your target that night.
You ordered to have me killed.
- Why would I do that?
- I don't know!
Maybe because
I'm getting ahead of you in business.
Or maybe you're getting satisfaction
whenever you see your rivals suffering.
Please, Garpidio...
You and your grandsons
should leave Florence alone.
We will never have a Ferell
become part of our family.
Never.
You're right.
I wanted to see you suffer.
I got mad at you
for not understanding that Amanda loved me.
I was disappointed
because I wanted to share that love
with my brother, my best friend.
But what did you do?
You looked at me as if I'm so evil.
When all I wanted to do was...
to love the person who loves me.
But I was wrong.
Instead of understanding
the pain you're feeling...
I was wrong to resent you.
If I can only bring back time...
I should've been a better friend to you.
That's why I won't get tired
of asking for your forgiveness.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for everything.
And because of that, I'm begging you.
All our pain and hard feelings...
let's not pass them on to the kids.
Why are you home late?
I just did something in school.
There are people I needed to talk to.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Do you think I'm here to play dumb?
I was with George earlier.
Remember him?
Camille's father.
He told me
about what happened between you and Camille.
The incident...
And it made him realize
that he needs to fix his relationship
with his daughter.
He told me you were instrumental
in making him realize that.
And I was so proud of you...
until he showed me this.
It looks like
you haven't informed your friends
not to post pictures with the Ferells.
Please let me explain.
Explain?
What else do we need to talk about?
We already have an agreement.
I already told you to avoid the Ferells.
I'm sorry, but...
I can't do what you want.
Because the Ferells are my friends.
Tristan, Aldus, Troy, and Owen
are my friends.
Grandpa Garp is close to my heart.
And most importantly, I love Nero.
You would rather choose those killers
than your own mother?
I don't believe in that.
Because I know Grandpa Garp is not capable
of what you're accusing him of.
Can you hear yourself?
They brainwashed you.
They made you believe their lies.
I am not dumb.
I have a mind of my own.
I also have my own understanding.
And if there's a victim here, that's you.
You're a victim of your own anger.
You're a victim of the pain you felt
when you lost Mommy.
Why?
Because you weren't able to protect her.
You failed to save her.
That's why you're looking
for someone else to blame
because of your own failure.
Because you knew deep in you
that you once neglected your family.
That's why you lost me, right?
Enough!
Go to your room!
Pack your bags.
I'm pulling you out of the university
and taking you with me to the States.
Are you sure where we're going?
We're getting lost already.
Don't pressure me.
That was 17 years ago.
Wait.
I remember something.
There. Wait, hold on.
- Okay, go.
- Yes, that's right.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
I don't need your help...
Unless you'll help me get inside
the mansion of the Almeros
to get Florence.
And then what?
You'll elope and live happily ever after?
Maybe that's another cartoon character.
No. This time, it's for real.
- Look, this is a real person.
- Let me see.
Federico, look at this.
This is the one.
Who is that?
Celestina!
Dad!
Where is she? Celestina is missing.
Lorenzo, it is your fault...
why Florence rebelled.
Florence?
What's happening?
I saw Florence.
Maybe your eyes are
just playing tricks on you.
I can't make a mistake.
I really saw her face.
Nero?